Guide to the Jon Lewis Photographs of the United Farm Workers Movement
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Jon Lewis photographs of the United Farm Workers movement
1966-2009
1966-1968
WA Photos 466
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
17.65
(53 boxes)
This collection consists of approximately eleven thousand photographs created by Jon Lewis that document the activities of César Chávez, the National Farm Workers Association, and United Farm Workers Organizing Committee in California, 1966-1971, as well as related publications and audiovisual materials, including videotapes and videodiscs, 1967-2009. Most images document activities related to the California Grape Strike in 1966.
Lewis, Jon, 1938-2009
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Gaylord Jon Lewis on the Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana, 2009-2010.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Associated Materials
Jon Lewis, Photographs and Film of César Chávez and Agricultural Labor Activities in California (WA Photos 81). Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Yale University.
Jon Lewis (1938-2009)
Gaylord Jon Lewis (1938-2009) was a photographer and printer in San Francisco, California. After service in the United States Marine Corps, Lewis earned a baccalaureate degree from San Jose State University. In 1966, Lewis joined the farm worker movement and documented the work and activities of César Chávez and the California Grape Strike. He later earned a graduate degree in photography at San Francisco State University.
United Farm Workers of America and the California Grape Strike
The United Farm Workers of America (UFWA) is a labor union created from the merging of the Agricultural Workers Organizing Committee (AWOC) led by Larry Itliong (1913-1977), Philip Vera Cruz (1904-1994), and others, with the National Farm Workers Association (NFWA) led by César Chávez (1927-1993) and Dolores Huerta (born 1930).
On September 8, 1965, the AWOC and its primarily Filipino membership started a strike against grape growers in Delano, California. During the strike they demanded salaries equal to the federal minimum wage. The predominantly Mexican-American NFWA joined the strike soon after it began. During the California Grape Strike and related boycott of table grapes, the AWOC and NFWA recognized their common goals and methods. On August 22, 1966, the groups combined to form the United Farm Workers Organizing Committee and became a member of the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations. The union eventually became the United Farm Workers of America. By 1970, the UFWA reached a collective bargaining agreement with the table-grape growers.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of approximately eleven thousand photographs created by Jon Lewis that document the activities of César Chávez, the National Farm Workers Association, and United Farm Workers Organizing Committee in California, 1966-1971, as well as related publications and audiovisual materials, 1967-2009. Most images document activities related to the California Grape Strike in 1966.
Images include migrant agricultural laborers during the picketing fields of table grape growers, including the Di Giorgio Fruit Corporation, in Delano, California, during the California Grape Strike. Other images related to the strikers depict the labor of farm workers, their housing, and the vineyards. A group of images depicts strikers picketing the arrival of Governor Edmund Gerald "Pat" Brown, Sr. at the meeting of the California Democratic Council in Bakersfield, California, February 1966. A significant group of images documents a visit to strikers by Senator Robert F. Kennedy in March 1966, as well as a related local hearing for the Senate Subcommittee on Migratory Labor that he conducted with Senators Harrison A. Williams and George L. Murphy in Delano. Groups of images also document college student volunteers supporting the strike during the summer of 1966.
Many images document a peregrinación (pilgrimage) march during the California Grape Strike from Delano to Sacramento, March-April 1966, including informal portraits of César Chávez; views of marchers and flag bearers holding flags for the National Farm Workers Association; and images of a banner that depicts the Catholic icon of the Virgin Mary known as Our Lady of Guadalupe. Related images to the peregrinación show volunteers and activities that provided material support for the march, including food caravans and temporary camps, as well as rallies held along the route of the march.
A substantial portion of images in the collection document performances of El Teatro Campesino, a theatrical troupe founded by Luis Valdez and Agustin Lira, which performed as a cultural arm of the National Farm Workers Association.
A small group of images depict César Chávez at an outdoor religious service during his Fast for Nonviolence at the Field Office of the United Farm Workers of America in Delano, also known as "Forty Acres," February-March 1968.
Few individuals involved with the strike are identified in the images. Individuals identified in the collection include César Chávez and his wife, Helen Chávez, as well as other members of the union leadership, including James L. Drake, Marshall Ganz, Dolores Huerta, Larry Itliong, Antonio Orendain, Gilbert Padilla, and Fred Ross.
Besides documenting the activities of the groups and individuals, the photographic material in the collection documents the evolution of images from negatives captured by Lewis to resultant prints and publications. The negatives and contact sheets show variant images captured by Lewis. The books and audiovisual materials document the in which ways Lewis and others used the images.
Arrangement
Organized into two series: I. Photographs, 1966-1971. II. Books and Audiovisual Materials, 1967-2009.
Agricultural industries -- California; Documentary films -- California; Guadalupe, Our Lady of -- Pictorial works; Grape Strike, Calif., 1965-1970 -- Pictorial works; Labor leaders -- United States -- Pictorial works; Labor unions -- United States -- Pictorial works; Mexican American labor union members -- Pictorial works; Migrant agricultural laborers -- California -- Pictorial works; Mexican American migrant agricultural laborers -- Pictorial works; Strikes and lockouts -- Agricultural laborers -- California -- Pictorial works; Delano (Calif.) -- Strike, 1965-66 -- Pictorial works; DVDs; DVD-Video discs; Negatives (photographs); Photographic prints; Slides (photographs); Videotapes; Chavez, Cesar, 1927-1993 -- Pictorial works; Huerta, Dolores, 1930- -- Pictorial works; Lewis, Jon, 1938-2009; Lewis, Jon, 1938-2009 -- Pictorial works; Lira, Agustín -- Pictorial works; Valdez, Luis -- Pictorial works; Di Giorgio Fruit Corporation -- Pictorial works; National Farm Workers Association -- Pictorial works; Teatro Campesino (Organization) -- Pictorial works; United Farm Workers Organizing Committee -- Pictorial works
- Photographs, 1966-1971; Series I; 15.4; (47 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Series I is organized into six subseries: Portfolios, Black and White Photographic Prints, Contact Prints, Negatives, Color Photographic Prints, and Color Slides.
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of photographs created by Lewis that depict the activities of the National Farm Workers Association, 1966-1971. The photographs are chiefly black and white, but include a small portion of color images, which Lewis also printed in black and white. Many images are duplicated across the various subseries.
  Many of the photographic prints in the Portfolios and Black and White Photographic Prints subseries have numbers written in pencil on their versos that reference the negative rolls for the original images, which are available in the Negative subseries, as well as their corresponding contact sheets in the Contact Sheets subseries. The sequence of these rolls within each subseries follow a roughly chronological arrangement.
  Some photographic prints in the Portfolios and Black and White Photographic Prints subseries also have pencil inscriptions of filenames written in pencil on their versos that reference digital surrogates created by the Farmworker Movement Documentation Project. CD-ROMS with these digital surrogates are in Series II.
  - Portfolios
    Arranged alphabetically.
    Groups of chiefly black and white photographic prints compiled by Lewis based on their general subject matter under titles applied by Lewis.
    - 1960s I, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1960s II, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Boycott Di Giorgio Fruit Corporation March in San Francisco, California, 1966 July 9 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - César Chávez I, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - César Chávez II, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - César Chávez Fast For Nonviolence, 1968 February-March (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Dolores Huerta, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Di Giorgio Fruit Corporation Phony Election, 1966 June 24 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Di Giorgio Fruit Corporation Election Organizing, 1966 August (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Di Giorgio Fruit Corporation Election Rally and Food Caravan from Sacramento to Delano, 1966 August (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Di Giorgio Fruit Corporation Election, 1966 August 30 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Environs and Detritus, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Faces I, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Faces II, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Fieldwork I, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Fieldwork II and Fieldscapes, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Infrastructure, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Kids I, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Kids II, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Leadership, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Peregrinación I, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Peregrinación II, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Peregrinación III, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Peregrinación IV, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Peregrinación V, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Picketing I, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Picketing II, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Picketing III, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Picketing IV, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Picketing V, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Picketing VI, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Robert F. Kennedy, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Summer for Student Volunteers, 1966 June (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Teatro Campesino I, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Teatro Campesino II, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Volunteers and Picketing Governor Edmund Gerald "Pat" Brown, Sr. in Bakersfield, California, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Black and White Photographic Prints
    Based on a preliminary comparison with the photographic negatives, the prints are arranged sequentially by negative roll number, followed by prints from unnumbered rolls, then by prints which were not matched to negatives, and then by oversize photographic prints.
    Most prints are 8 by 10 inches in size. The images chiefly derive from rolls in the Negatives subseries, while some photographic prints derive from color slides, which are in the available in the Color Slides subseries.
    Many of the images have duplicate prints. Identified prints without pencil inscriptions on their verso have been filed with their corresponding roll number.
    - Rolls 1-25, 1966 (Box 6)
    - Rolls 26-50, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Rolls 51-65, 1966 (Box 8)
    - Rolls 66-75, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Rolls 76-85, 1966 (Box 10)
    - Rolls 86-100, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Rolls 101-119, 1966 (Box 12)
    - Rolls 120-130, 1966 (Box 13)
    - Rolls 131-147, 1966 (Box 14)
    - Rolls 147-165, 1966 (Box 15)
    - Rolls 166-190, 1966 (Box 16)
    - Rolls 191-215, 1966 (Box 17)
    - Rolls 216-230, 1966 (Box 18)
    - Rolls 231-285, 1966 (Box 19)
    - Rolls 286-299, 1966 (Box 20)
    - Unnumbered Rolls, 1966-1968 (Box 21)
    - Unidentified Photographic Prints, 1966-1968 (Box 22–27)
      Each folder holds a single image. Many images have many duplicate prints.
    - Unsorted Oversize Photographic Prints, 1966-1968 (Box 28 Oversize)
  - Contact Prints
    Arranged sequentially by roll number followed by sheets from unnumbered rolls.
    Black and white contact prints of 35 millimeter negatives created and compiled by Lewis.
    - Rolls 1-25, 1966 (Box 29)
    - Rolls 26-50, 1966 (Box 30)
    - Rolls 51-75, 1966 (Box 31)
    - Rolls 76-100, 1966 (Box 32)
    - Rolls 101-125, 1966 (Box 33)
    - Rolls 126-150, 1966 (Box 34)
    - Rolls 151-175, 1966 (Box 35)
    - Rolls 176-200, 1966 (Box 36)
    - Rolls 201-225, 1966 (Box 37)
    - Rolls 226-250, 1966 (Box 38)
    - Rolls 251-275, 1966 (Box 39)
      The numbering for rolls is repeated in this box. This includes two rolls for each of the numbers 257, 259, and 262, as well as three rolls with the number 260.
    - Rolls 276-291, 1966 (Box 40)
      The numbering for rolls is repeated in this box. This includes two rolls at each of the numbers 286 and 291.
    - Sheets for Unnumbered Rolls, 1966-1968 (Box 41)
  - Negatives
    Arranged sequentially by roll number followed by unnumbered rolls.
    Chiefly black and white negatives created and compiled by Lewis. Lewis often spliced negatives from different sequences of original images together into discrete "rolls."
    - Rolls 1-200, 1966 (Box 42)
      Roll 33 includes sixteen color negatives.
    - Rolls 201-301, 1966 (Box 43)
      The numbering for rolls is repeated in this box. This includes two rolls for each of the numbers 259, 260, 262, and 286.
    - Unnumbered Rolls, 1966-1968 (Box 44)
  - Color Photographic Prints
    Arranged alphabetically by subject.
    This subseries consists of color photographic prints that range in size from four by six inches to twelve by eighteen inches.
    Some images are duplicated in the subseries Color Slides.
    - César Chávez, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 37-47)
    - Peregrinación, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 48-74)
    - Picket Lines, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 75)
    - Portraits, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 76)
    - Oversize Prints
      - César Chávez, 1966 (Box 46 Oversize, Folder 77)
      - Peregrinación, 1966 (Box 46 Oversize, Folder 78)
  - Color Slides
    Arranged with a slide show compiled by Lewis, followed by color slides with printed dates on their mounts, and then color slides arranged alphabetically by subject.
    This subseries consists chiefly of color thirty-five millimeter slides. Some images are duplicated in the subseries Color Photographic Prints, as well as the subseries Black and White Photographic Prints.
    - Slide show, "Hasta Sacramento...: The 1966 Peregrinación as Seen by Jon Lewis" (Box 47, Folder 79-80)
      Accompanied by photographic prints of the slide show.
    - Color Slides with Printing Dates, 1966 March-1971 September (Box 47, Folder 81-93)
    - Color Slides by Subject
      - César Chávez, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 94)
      - Farm Worker Housing, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 95)
      - Fields, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 96)
      - Peregrinación, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 97)
      - Picket Lines, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 98)
      - Portraits, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 99)
      - Rallies, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 100)
      - El Teatro Campesino, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 101)
      - Copy Photograph of the Our Lady of Guadalupe icon, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 102)
- Books and Audiovisual Materials, 1967-2009; Series II; 2.25; (6 boxes)
  Series II is organized into two subseries: Books and Audiovisual Materials by Lewis and Materials by Others
  This series consists of publications and audiovisual materials created by Lewis and others that used his photographs.
  - Books and Audiovisual Materials by Lewis
    Arranged chronologically by the first date of publication of the material by Lewis.
    - La Huelga De La Uva En Delano: The Strike of the Grape in Delano, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 103)
    - From This Earth ... of the Delano Grape Strike, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 104-105)
      - Covers, title page, and advertisement clipping, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 106)
      - Draft letter to "Ed", 2008 October 25 (Box 48, Folder 107)
        Discusses creating a digital version of the book for Luis Valdez.
    - Nosotros Venceremos, 1971; Running time: 11 minutes
      The documentary film Nosotros Venceremos (We shall overcome) with the opening title of "La huelga de la uva en Delano" (The strike of the grape in Delano) was produced by Lewis in 1971 and was used as a promotional tool by the United Farm Workers Organizing Committee.
      The film documents the events of 1966 using photographic imagery that depicts picket lines, individual farm workers, the peregrinación march from Delano to Sacramento, the Fast for Nonviolence by Chávez, and the announcement of a contract between the union and growers with a soundtrack of hymns and speeches in Spanish recorded by Eliezer Lozada Risco.
      - Broadside, circa 1985 (Box 48, Folder 108)
      - [Video recording], circa 1985 (Box 49, Folder 109-110)
      - [Videodisc], 2004 (Box 50, Folder 111-119)
  - Materials by Others
    Arranged chronologically by the first date of publication of the material.
    - Rodrigo Terronez Memorial Clinic
      Biographical/Historical note
      The Rodrigo Terronez Memorial Clinic is a medical clinic for farm workers in Delano, California, operated by the United Farm Workers of America.
      - Flyer Soliciting Donations, circa 1970 (Box 48, Folder 120)
    - Farmworker Movement Documentation Project
      Founded in 2003 by LeRoy Chatfield, the Farmworker Movement Documentation Project compiles and publishes primary source accounts from the volunteers who worked with César Chávez to build his farm worker movement from 1962 to 1993.
      - CD-ROMS, 2004 August 30-2009 December 29
        Immediate Source of Acquisition
        CD-ROMS with digital surrogates of photographs created by Lewis and used by the project in publications and its web site.
        - MARCH TO SACRAMENTO 40 COLOR / VARIOUS SIZE JON LEWIS, 2010-wa-34440-0001; 1 (Box 52)
          Conditions Governing Access
          Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
        - JON LEWIS Photos, 2010-wa-34440-0002; 1 (Box 52)
        - JON LEWIS 27 COLOR 95 B / W, 2010-wa-34440-0003; 1 (Box 52)
        - Jon Lewis Photos of Cesar, 2010-wa-34440-0004; 1 (Box 52)
        - Jon Lewis Portraits of Farmworkers **5th Photo is sized wrong, 2010-wa-34440-0005; 1 (Box 52)
        - Jon Lewis Color Photos of the March to Sacramento Part I, 2010-wa-34440-0006; 1 (Box 52)
        - Jon Lewis Color Photos of the March to Sacramento Part II, 2010-wa-34440-0007; 1 (Box 52)
        - Jon Lewis Photos - Slides Jim Scanned jpeg's 300 dpi 4000 pixels, 2010-wa-34440-0008; 1 (Box 52)
        - Jon Lewis Slides Jim scanned Jpeg & Tiff 300 dpi, 2010-wa-34440-0009; 1 (Box 52)
        - Jon Lewis, 2010-wa-34440-0010; 1 (Box 52)
        - Jon Lewis, 2010-wa-34440-0011; 1 (Box 52)
        - Pro Scans 4000 ppi w/ ICE Jon Lewis Slides .tif files, 2010-wa-34440-0012; 1 (Box 52)
        - For Jim Photos for March to Sacramento Chapter Jon Lewis dvd, 2010-wa-34440-0013; 1 (Box 52)
        - 10/06 JON LEWIS Photos INCLUDES: DELANO STRIKERS, 2010-wa-34440-0014; 1 (Box 52)
        - Additional Jon Lewis B/W photos of farmworkers Scanned by Sand Flea Studios + word file with inscriptions on backs of photos 1) 600 ppi tif 2) 300 ppi jpeg 3) 100 ppi jpeg sized @ 500 pixels for web, 2010-wa-34440-0015; 1 (Box 52)
        - SFS Scans of Jon Lewis photos DISK 1 of 3 600 ppi tif + 300 ppi jpeg 2/9/07 Cesar, Children, RFK, Fieldscape, Volunteers, 2010-wa-34440-0016; 1 (Box 52)
        - SFS Scans of Jon Lewis photos DISK 2 of 3 600 ppi tif + 300 ppi jpeg 2/9/07 Dolores- photos 001-025, 2010-wa-34440-0017; 1 (Box 52)
        - SFS Scans of Jon Lewis photos Disk 3 of 3 600 ppi tif + 300 ppi jpeg + 96 ppi jpeg 2/9/07 Dolores 026-033, f.w., Leaders, WEB sized (All), inscriptions (All), 2010-wa-34440-0018; 1 (Box 52)
        - Cesar w/ banner 1st scanned, 2010-wa-34440-0019; 1 (Box 51)
        - JON LEWIS duplicate of Cesar w / banner, 2010-wa-34440-0020; 1 (Box 51)
        - LEWIS Sr Huerta, 2010-wa-34440-0021; 1 (Box 51)
        - 1st 39 slides duplicate, 2010-wa-34440-0022; 1 (Box 51)
        - 1st 39 slides duplicate, 2010-wa-34440-0023; 1 (Box 51)
        - duplicate of 1st bath of slides, 2010-wa-34440-0024; 1 (Box 51)
        - Jon Lewis Portfolio I 18 Photos Andres 7-14-05, 2010-wa-34440-0025; 1 (Box 51)
        - sundry Cesars - color, 2010-wa-34440-0026; 1 (Box 51)
        - Lewis hi res Cesar tight head shot 8x10 100 MB Tiff, 2010-wa-34440-0027; 1 (Box 51)
        - slideshow originals Jon Lewis Photos, 2010-wa-34440-0028; 1 (Box 51)
        - LEWIS hires Cesar (tight head shot) 27 MB Tif, 2010-wa-34440-0029; 1 (Box 51)
        - 1st 40 slides, 2010-wa-34440-0030; 1 (Box 51)
        - LEWIS Dolores, 2010-wa-34440-0031; 1 (Box 51)
        - 7 jpegs Cesar Jon Lewis, 2010-wa-34440-0032; 1 (Box 51)
        - Rayko, 2010-wa-34440-0033; 1 (Box 51)
        - 3 Color Photos of Cesar, 2010-wa-34440-0034; 1 (Box 51)
        - Pro Scans 4000 ppi w/ ICE Jon Lewis Slides .tif files, 2010-wa-34440-0035; 1 (Box 51)
        - Sand Flea Studios Scans of Jon Lewis Photos & Slides DVD R?, 2010-wa-34440-0036; 1 (Box 51)
        - high res. Cesars hi res Cesars 2 B&W, 2010-wa-34440-0037; 1 (Box 51)
        - Additional Jon Lewis B/W photos of farmworkers (Scanned by Sand Flea Studios) 1) 600 ppi tifs 2) 300 ppi jpegs 3) 100 ppi jpegs sized @ 500 pixels for web 4) Photo inscriptions, 2010-wa-34440-0038; 1 (Box 51)
        - 2007 JON LEWIS DIGIORGIO + DELANO FOOD CARAVAN, 2010-wa-34440-0039; 1 (Box 51)
        - SFS Scans of Jon Lewis photos DISK 1 of 3 600 ppi tif + 300 ppi jpeg 2/9/07 Cesar, Children, RFK, Fieldscape, Volunteers, 2010-wa-34440-0040; 1 (Box 51)
        - SFS Scans of Jon Lewis photos DISK 2 of 3 600 ppi tif + 300 ppi jpeg 2/9/07 Dolores - photos 001-025, 2010-wa-34440-0041; 1 (Box 51)
        - SFS Scans of Jon Lewis photos DISK 3 of 3 600 ppi tif + 300 ppi jpeg + 96 ppi jpeg 2/9/07 Dolores 026-033, F.W., leaders, WEB sized (All), inscriptions (All), 2010-wa-34440-0042; 1 (Box 51)
        - LeRoy Chatfield Photo Files April 20, 2007 JON LEWIS Photos NFWA SUMMER Project 1966, 2010-wa-34440-0043; 1 (Box 51)
        - JON LEWIS Photos DiGiorgio Phony ELECTION, 2010-wa-34440-0044; 1 (Box 51)
        - JON LEWIS CESAR CHAVEZ PORTRAIT 4 SCANS, 2010-wa-34440-0045; 1 (Box 51)
        - JON LEWIS 1966 DIGIORGIO, 2010-wa-34440-0046; 1 (Box 51)
        - LEWIS Cesar w/ type, 2010-wa-34440-0047; 1 (Box 51)
        - JON LEWIS DIGIORGIO VOTE, 2010-wa-34440-0048; 1 (Box 51)
        - First few days on picket line Jan. '66, 2010-wa-34440-0049; 1 (Box 51)
        - Miscellaneous, extraneous, + subcutaneous SLIDES Color Slides, 2010-wa-34440-0050; 1 (Box 51)
        - '68 fast 7 scans, 2010-wa-34440-0051; 1 (Box 51)
        - JON LEWIS NFWA STRIKE HDQTS JON LEWIS NFWA STRIKE HDQTS 1966, 2010-wa-34440-0052; 1 (Box 51)
        - JON LEWIS - EGBROWN MISC JON LEWIS EGBROWN MISC 1966, 2010-wa-34440-0053; 1 (Box 51)
        - JON LEWIS PHOTOS JULY 26, 2008 "JONL PICKET LINE-I" FARMWORKER MOVEMENT DOCUMENTATION PROJECT, 2010-wa-34440-0054; 1 (Box 51)
        - JON LEWIS THE FAST JON LEWIS THE FAST 7/12/08, 2010-wa-34440-0055; 1 (Box 51)
        - JON LEWIS -FILIPINO BROTHERS -PICKET LINE -LIVING CONDITIONS 8/3/08, 2010-wa-34440-0056; 1 (Box 51)
        - JON LEWIS FIELDSCAPE-PICKETLINE DELANO STRIKERS FWLIVING DETRITUS UNION LABEL 8/4/08, 2010-wa-34440-0057; 1 (Box 51)
        - RFK, 2010-wa-34440-0058; 1 (Box 51)
        - JON LEWIS AFTER MARCH (I) + RFK RESTORED PHOTO 8/23/08, 2010-wa-34440-0059; 1 (Box 51)
        - JON LEWIS AFTER MARCH 2 A 8/27/08, 2010-wa-34440-0060; 1 (Box 51)
        - title shot, 2010-wa-34440-0061; 1 (Box 51)
        - Jon Lewis Scanning @ 4,000 dpi with corrections 63 - 124 10.10.08, 2010-wa-34440-0062; 1 (Box 51)